FASHION DESIGNER

PROFILE

My name is Megan Rodgers and I am currently studying at Kent State University for Fashion Design and have a bachelor's degree in Fashion Merchandising. I was chosen as one of the top 20 students in my Junior class to submit for CFDA and Joes Black Book. With my education and experience, I would be an assest to your company in the Assistant Designer position. As a Design Assistant at Ellery Homestyles, I was described as having an "insane work ethic." I demonstrated that I had an eye for color and design and could be trusted to get the job don

EDUCATION

FASHION DESIGN

Kent State University 2017 - 2020

SUSTAINABLE DESIGN ENTREPRENEUR

F.I.T - Continued Education 2016 - 2017

FASHION MERCHANDISING

Kent State University 2012 - 2016

SKILLS

ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE
MACHINE KNITTING
DIGITAL KNITTING
TEXTILE DESIGN
MS OFFICE
BLUECHERRY - PLM SYSTEM

WEBSITE

WWW.MEGANRODGERS.ME

EXPERIENCE

DESIGN INTERN - SWEATER DEPARTMENT

Ann Taylor / New York, NY / June 2019 - Aug. 2019

- Spearheaded the design of a capsule collection for a Λ nn Taylor Intern presentation to high-level executives at the end of the internship
- Collaborated with Ann Taylor interns to target new customers
- Created Fall 2020 techpacks for Sweater Creative Design team
- Assisted in fit meetings, sketch reviews and Spring '20 P.O.V review
- Organized the Spring and Fall 2020 concept and line boards for sweater design team

DESIGN ASSISTANT - WINDOW/BLANKET Ellery Homestyles / New York, NY / Aug. 2016 - Aug. 2017

- Created tech packs for all Window and Blanket production samples on the PLM system BlueCherry
- Worked alongside Window Design team while designing upcoming market doing trend, color and fabric reserach, attending tradeshows and trend presentations
- Oversaw communication with overseas production team and requested production samples, matches lab-dips and approved strike-off samples to ensure desired production quality $\frac{1}{2} \left(\frac{1}{2} \right) = \frac{1}{2} \left(\frac{1}{2} \right) \left(\frac$

DESIGN INTERN - BEDDING DEPARTMENT

Ellery Homestyles / New York, NY / June 2015 - Aug. 2015

- Assembled presentation boards and pulled fabric samples for buyer meetings $\,$
- Created and prepared engravings, mappings and pre-techs for Waverly, VUE, Historic Charleston, Belk and Blissliving collections to send overseas for production
- Controlled the design and production of nine pillows for the Jilo bedding collection for Belk
- Certified on the company's PLM System, Blue Cherry

SERVER

91 Woodfired Oven / Canton, OH / Sept. 2017 - Present

- Oversaw many parties of varying sizes
- Assisted guests in order selection by promoting monthly feature items
- Coordinated with kitchen staff to ensure timely and accurate order preparation
- Continually expanding list of positive guest feedback
- Responsible for opening / closing and overseeing servers to ensure closing and sidework procedures are completed